<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LySining</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hc">"The Lyceum of the Philippines University - Cavite Harmonic Chorale also known as LPU HC or simply HC, is one of the major organizations based in LPU Cavite. Its former conductor and musical director was Mr. Oliver M. Lee. It\'s just a starting group founded last June 2008 with a 20 starting members which apparently turns out into a big musical family with few batches of apprentices. Despite the fact that it’s new, they become competitive in the chorale industry.
        \n\nThe group had undergone different chorale workshops held at Cultural Center of the Philippines under the hands of the Philippine Madrigal Singers and was invited twice to sing in a chorale presentation entitled "Latina America 2011" and "Madz Et Al 2012" at the PhilAm Life Theater together with other selected chorale groups all over the Philippines. Have presented several musical and cultural pieces and play in LPU Cavite like "Walang Sugat", "LPU Cavite Dance Company Dance Concert", "126th Anniversary of Banda Matanda", and "What\'s on your Mind?".
        \n\nThough it’s new and yet in the process or at the stage of improving and developing musical ability and vocal techniques, the group made their names in the industry. In fact, last 2009 (one year after it was founded) the group bagged the 1st place in the chorale competition held at Trece Martires City in Cavite featuring cultural exchange. In addition, the group has also won the 1st place to their most recent chorale competition held at Tagaytay Highlands, Tagaytay City entitled "Carols in the Sky" last December 2011.
After the resignation of Mr. Oliver M. Lee, he was replace by Mr. Ariel Cabral as conductor and musical director from 2013 to 2015.
        \n\nLast July 2015, Mr. Warlito S. Yalung, an alumnus of Philippine Madrigal Singers took over the LPU Harmonic Chorale and continues to grow as its best with its new conductor.\n"</string>
</resources>
